就像我之前说的一样，早期的Android版本
As I said before, early versions of Android
是没有加载器模式的。原先被弃用的模式
didn't have the loader model. The original deprecated model
造成了帧速率下降，使得许多应用不得不重新查询数据库
caused frame rate drops whenever many applications had to
即便是一个简单的应用，所得到的数据库也比我们在Sunshine应用中
re-query their databases. Even simple ones. Databases get far
拥有的复杂得多
more complex than what we have here in
所以第一个答案是确定的
Sunshine. So the first answer is a definite yes.
我们注意到像AsyncTask这样是如何与UI界面相连接的
We noted how things like AsyncTask are bound to
所以就算是一个细微的方向改变也会杀死查询进程
the UI, so something as little as an orientation
因此，另一个答案也是确定的
change could kill the query. So that's another definite
所以第三个选项肯定是错误的
yes. So the third option is just a non-starter.